Bedau, Hugo A.; Papers apap199
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- Subject Files, 1955-2003; 4; 16.79 cubic ft.
  - Geographic Files, 1953-2002; 4.3
    - California, 1960-1963 (Box 12 (4-Subject Files), Folder 15)
    - California, West's Annotated Penal Codes, 1970 (Box 12 (4-Subject Files), Folder 16)
    - California, Death Penalty Proposition, 1972 (Box 12 (4-Subject Files), Folder 17)
    - California, 1983-1989 (Box 12 (4-Subject Files), Folder 18)
    - Connecticut, "Capital Punishment in Connecticut after Furman v. Georgia", 1973 (Box 12 (4-Subject Files), Folder 19)
      Also transcript of Judiciary Committee, February 15, 1973.
    - Connecticut, 1989-1990 (Box 12 (4-Subject Files), Folder 20)
    - Delaware, 1958 (Box 12 (4-Subject Files), Folder 21)
    - Delaware Supreme Court, 1972 (Box 12 (4-Subject Files), Folder 22)
    - Delaware, 1985-1986 (Box 12 (4-Subject Files), Folder 23)
    - Florida Death Penalty, 1965 (Box 13 (4-Subject Files), Folder 1)
    - Florida Report on Capital Punishment, 1971 (Box 13 (4-Subject Files), Folder 2)
    - Florida, "Analysis of Political Attitudes towards the Death Penalty in the State of Florida", Amnesty International, 1986 (Box 13 (4-Subject Files), Folder 3)
    - Florida, 1983-1989 (Box 13 (4-Subject Files), Folder 4)
    - Georgia Capital Punishment, 1965 (Box 13 (4-Subject Files), Folder 5)
    - Georgia, 1983-1989 (Box 13 (4-Subject Files), Folder 6)
    - Idaho, 1989 (Box 13 (4-Subject Files), Folder 7)
    - Illinois Legislative Council, 1951 (Box 13 (4-Subject Files), Folder 8)
    - Illinois Legislative Council, 1954 (Box 13 (4-Subject Files), Folder 9)
    - Illinois -- Death Penalty in Cook County, from 1977 through 1980, 1984 (Box 13 (4-Subject Files), Folder 10)
    - Illinois, 1984-1986 (Box 13 (4-Subject Files), Folder 11)
    - Indiana, 1984 (Box 13 (4-Subject Files), Folder 12)
    - Iowa, 1990 (Box 13 (4-Subject Files), Folder 13)
    - Kansas, 1963 (Box 13 (4-Subject Files), Folder 14)
    - Kentucky Capital Punishment, 1965 (Box 13 (4-Subject Files), Folder 15)
    - Kentucky, 1983 (Box 13 (4-Subject Files), Folder 16)
    - Louisiana, 1983-1988 (Box 13 (4-Subject Files), Folder 17)
    - Maryland Report of Committee on Capital Punishment, 1962 (Box 13 (4-Subject Files), Folder 18)
    - Maryland, 1984 (Box 13 (4-Subject Files), Folder 19)
    - Massachusetts, "Analysis of Murder Convictions in Massachusetts 1900-1962", 1963 (Box 13 (4-Subject Files), Folder 20)
    - Massachusetts, 1965 (Box 13 (4-Subject Files), Folder 21)
    - Massachusetts, 1967 (Box 13 (4-Subject Files), Folder 22)
    - Massachusetts Journal Articles, 1968-1982 (Box 13 (4-Subject Files), Folder 23-24)
    - Massachusetts, 1970 (Box 13 (4-Subject Files), Folder 25)
    - Massachusetts, 1971 (Box 13 (4-Subject Files), Folder 26)
    - Massachusetts, 1972 (Box 13 (4-Subject Files), Folder 27)
    - Massachusetts, 1973 (Box 13 (4-Subject Files), Folder 28)
    - Massachusetts, 1974 (Box 13 (4-Subject Files), Folder 29)
    - Massachusetts, 1975 (Box 13 (4-Subject Files), Folder 30)
    - Massachusetts, 1976 (Box 13 (4-Subject Files), Folder 31)
    - Massachusetts, Survey Research, 1976-1982 (Box 13 (4-Subject Files), Folder 32)
    - Massachusetts, 1977 (Box 13 (4-Subject Files), Folder 33)
    - Massachusetts, 1978 (Box 13 (4-Subject Files), Folder 34)
    - Massachusetts, 1979 (Box 13 (4-Subject Files), Folder 35)
    - Massachusetts, 1980 (Box 13 (4-Subject Files), Folder 36)
    - Massachusetts, 1982 (Box 13 (4-Subject Files), Folder 37)
    - Massachusetts, 1983 (Box 13 (4-Subject Files), Folder 38)
    - Massachusetts, 1984 (Box 13 (4-Subject Files), Folder 39)
    - Massachusetts, 1985 (Box 13 (4-Subject Files), Folder 40)
    - Massachusetts, 1986 (Box 13 (4-Subject Files), Folder 41)
    - Massachusetts, 1989 (Box 13 (4-Subject Files), Folder 42)
    - Massachusetts, 1990 (Box 13 (4-Subject Files), Folder 43)
    - Massachusetts, 1991 (Box 14 (4-Subject Files), Folder 1)
    - Massachusetts, 1992 (Box 14 (4-Subject Files), Folder 2)
    - Massachusetts, 1994 (Box 14 (4-Subject Files), Folder 3-4)
    - Massachusetts, 1996 (Box 14 (4-Subject Files), Folder 5)
    - Massachusetts, 1997 (Box 14 (4-Subject Files), Folder 6)
    - Massachusetts, 1999 (Box 14 (4-Subject Files), Folder 7)
    - Massachusetts, 2000-2001 (Box 14 (4-Subject Files), Folder 8)
    - Massachusetts, SJC Advisory Opinion (Box 14 (4-Subject Files), Folder 9)
    - Michigan, 1982-1999 (Box 14 (4-Subject Files), Folder 10)
    - Minnesota, 1988 (Box 14 (4-Subject Files), Folder 11)
    - Mississippi, 1982-1989 (Box 14 (4-Subject Files), Folder 12)
    - Nebraska, 1977-1984 (Box 14 (4-Subject Files), Folder 13)
    - New Jersey Report on Capital Punishment, 1908 (Box 14 (4-Subject Files), Folder 14)
    - New Jersey, Capital Punishment in New Jersey, 1664-1950, 1951 (Box 14 (4-Subject Files), Folder 15)
    - New Jersey Public Hearing, 1957 (Box 14 (4-Subject Files), Folder 16)
    - New Jersey Testimony before Assembly Judiciary Committee, 1958 (Box 14 (4-Subject Files), Folder 17)
    - New Jersey, 1958 (Box 14 (4-Subject Files), Folder 18-19)
    - New Jersey, 1959 (Box 14 (4-Subject Files), Folder 20)
    - New Jersey, 1960 (Box 14 (4-Subject Files), Folder 21)
    - New Jersey Parole Board, 1960-1961 (Box 14 (4-Subject Files), Folder 22)
    - New Jersey Report on Capital Punishment, 1964 (Box 14 (4-Subject Files), Folder 23)
    - New Jersey Public Hearing, 1964 (Box 14 (4-Subject Files), Folder 24)
    - New Jersey Capital Punishment, 1971 (Box 14 (4-Subject Files), Folder 25)
    - New Jersey Public Hearing before Judiciary Committee, 1972 (Box 14 (4-Subject Files), Folder 26)
    - New Jersey Policy Conference Report, 1992 (Box 14 (4-Subject Files), Folder 27-28)
    - New York, 1939 (Box 15 (4-Subject Files), Folder 1)
    - New York State Special Report on Capital Punishment, 1965 (Box 15 (4-Subject Files), Folder 2)
    - New York Brief urging Abolition of Capital Punishment, 1962 (Box 15 (4-Subject Files), Folder 3)
    - New York, 1984 (Box 15 (4-Subject Files), Folder 4)
    - New York, 1990-1995 (Box 15 (4-Subject Files), Folder 5)
    - North Carolina, 1977; 1990 (Box 15 (4-Subject Files), Folder 6)
    - North Carolina Race and the Death Penalty, 2001 (Box 15 (4-Subject Files), Folder 7)
    - Ohio Capital Punishment, 1961 (Box 15 (4-Subject Files), Folder 8)
    - Ohio "Capital Punishment Legislative Implications of U.S. Supreme Court Decision Furman v. Georgia", 1972 (Box 15 (4-Subject Files), Folder 9)
    - Oklahoma, 1976 (Box 15 (4-Subject Files), Folder 10)
    - Oregon, 1964 (Box 15 (4-Subject Files), Folder 11)
    - Pennsylvania -- Home Town Hangings in the County Jails of Pennsylvania, 1834-1913, ca. 1960 (Box 15 (4-Subject Files), Folder 12)
    - Pennsylvania Report of the Joint Legislative Committee on Capital Punishment, 1961 (Box 15 (4-Subject Files), Folder 13)
    - Pennsylvania History of Executions and Commutations, 1915-1962 (Box 15 (4-Subject Files), Folder 14)
    - Pennsylvania -- Sentencing of First Degree Murders in Pennsylvania, 1960-1972 (Box 15 (4-Subject Files), Folder 15)
    - Pennsylvania Governor's Report on Capital Punishment, 1973 (Box 15 (4-Subject Files), Folder 16)
    - Pennsylvania -- List of Executions, 1834-1916 (Box 15 (4-Subject Files), Folder 17)
    - Rhode Island, 1978-1979 (Box 15 (4-Subject Files), Folder 18)
    - South Carolina Death Penalty Report, 1974 (Box 15 (4-Subject Files), Folder 19)
    - Tennessee, 1981 (Box 15 (4-Subject Files), Folder 20)
    - Texas, 1976-1989 (Box 15 (4-Subject Files), Folder 21)
    - Texas, 1990 (Box 15 (4-Subject Files), Folder 22)
    - Texas, Representation in Capital Cases in Texas, 1993 (Box 15 (4-Subject Files), Folder 23)
    - Texas, Death Penalty in Texas, Texas Civil Rights Project, 2000 (Box 15 (4-Subject Files), Folder 24)
    - Utah, 1978 (Box 15 (4-Subject Files), Folder 25)
    - Vermont, 1974 (Box 15 (4-Subject Files), Folder 26)
    - Washington, 1960; 1989 (Box 15 (4-Subject Files), Folder 27)
    - Wisconsin Capital Punishment, 1962 (Box 15 (4-Subject Files), Folder 28)
    - Wisconsin, "The Death Penalty: Legal Status Since Furman", 1973 (Box 15 (4-Subject Files), Folder 29)
    - Wyoming, 1990 (Box 15 (4-Subject Files), Folder 30)
    - Brazil, 1989 (Box 15 (4-Subject Files), Folder 31)
    - Canada, 1973-1986 (Box 15 (4-Subject Files), Folder 32)
    - Chile, 1984 (Box 15 (4-Subject Files), Folder 33)
    - China, 1983-1986 (Box 15 (4-Subject Files), Folder 34)
    - Czechoslovakia, 1984 (Box 15 (4-Subject Files), Folder 35)
    - Egypt, 1989 (Box 15 (4-Subject Files), Folder 36)
    - France, 1983 (Box 15 (4-Subject Files), Folder 37)
    - Germany, 1981-1984 (Box 15 (4-Subject Files), Folder 38)
    - Ghana, 1986 (Box 15 (4-Subject Files), Folder 39)
    - Great Britain, 1973-1983 (Box 15 (4-Subject Files), Folder 40)
    - Grenada, 1986 (Box 15 (4-Subject Files), Folder 41)
    - Guinea-Bissau, 1986 (Box 15 (4-Subject Files), Folder 42)
    - Holland, 1983 (Box 15 (4-Subject Files), Folder 43)
    - India, 1983-1989 (Box 15 (4-Subject Files), Folder 44)
    - Indonesia (Box 15 (4-Subject Files), Folder 45)
    - Iran, 1983-1989 (Box 15 (4-Subject Files), Folder 46)
    - Israel, 1984-1988 (Box 15 (4-Subject Files), Folder 47)
    - Jamaica, 1984 (Box 15 (4-Subject Files), Folder 48)
    - Japan, 1983-1990 (Box 15 (4-Subject Files), Folder 49)
    - Lebanon, 1984-1986 (Box 15 (4-Subject Files), Folder 50)
    - Liberia, 1984 (Box 15 (4-Subject Files), Folder 51)
    - Libya, 1988 (Box 15 (4-Subject Files), Folder 52)
    - Malaysia, 1986-1989 (Box 15 (4-Subject Files), Folder 53)
    - Namibia, 1989 (Box 15 (4-Subject Files), Folder 54)
    - Nigeria, 1984 (Box 15 (4-Subject Files), Folder 55)
    - Pakistan, 1985 (Box 15 (4-Subject Files), Folder 56)
    - Philippines, 1984 (Box 15 (4-Subject Files), Folder 57)
    - Romania, 1974; 1990 (Box 15 (4-Subject Files), Folder 58)
    - South Africa, 1983-1989 (Box 15 (4-Subject Files), Folder 59)
    - Soviet Union, 1983-1989 (Box 15 (4-Subject Files), Folder 60)
    - Spain, 1983 (Box 15 (4-Subject Files), Folder 61)
    - Syria, 1985 (Box 15 (4-Subject Files), Folder 62)
    - Thailand, 1986 (Box 15 (4-Subject Files), Folder 63)
    - Turkey, 1984 (Box 15 (4-Subject Files), Folder 64)
    - Vietnam, 1985 (Box 15 (4-Subject Files), Folder 65)
    - Yugoslavia, 1986 (Box 15 (4-Subject Files), Folder 66)
    - Zimbabwe, 1986 (Box 15 (4-Subject Files), Folder 67)
    - International, General, 1971 (Box 15 (4-Subject Files), Folder 68)
    - International, General, 1972 (Box 15 (4-Subject Files), Folder 69)
    - International, General, 1974 (Box 15 (4-Subject Files), Folder 70)
    - International, General, 1976 (Box 15 (4-Subject Files), Folder 71)
    - International, General, 1977 (Box 15 (4-Subject Files), Folder 72)
    - International, General, 1979 (Box 15 (4-Subject Files), Folder 73)
    - International, General, 1980 (Box 15 (4-Subject Files), Folder 74)
    - International, General, 1981 (Box 15 (4-Subject Files), Folder 75)
    - International, General, 1982 (Box 15 (4-Subject Files), Folder 76)
  - Audio/Visual, 1993-2001; Undated; 4.4
    This subseries contains VHS and cassette tapes on the subject of capital punishment.
    - Cassette Tapes, 1996; Undated; 4.4.1
      - "Execution by Reques", Kai Ryssdal (Box 16 (4.4.1-Cassette Tapes), Folder 1)
      - Live From Death Row the Case of Mumia Abu-Jamal/ 14 Annual Socialist Scholars Conference, 1996 (Box 16 (4.4.1-Cassette Tapes), Folder 2)
      - Public Radio, Execution Tapes (Box 16 (4.4.1-Cassette Tapes), Folder 3)
      - Marketplace Death Penalty (four tapes) (Box 16 (4.4.1-Cassette Tapes), Folder 4)
    - VHS, 1993-2001; Undated; 4.4.2
      - A&E Investigative Reports: Death Penalty on Trial (Box 17 (4.4.2-VHS), Folder 1)
      - Capital Punishment (Box 17 (4.4.2-VHS), Folder 2)
      - Debate on Capital Punishment, William Homans Jr. Endowment, 1996 November (Box 17 (4.4.2-VHS), Folder 3)
      - "Double Justice: Race and Capital Punishment", ACLU, NAACP and LDF, 1993; 2 copies (Box 17 (4.4.2-VHS), Folder 4)
      - Headliners and Legends with Matt Lauer: Timothy McVeigh, 2001 May (Box 17 (4.4.2-VHS), Folder 5)
      - MSNBC Investigates: Death Row Diary, 2001 April (Box 17 (4.4.2-VHS), Folder 6)
      - MSNBC Investigates: "Mercy for a Murderer?", 2001 February (Box 17 (4.4.2-VHS), Folder 7)
      - MSNBC Reports: Witness to the Execution, 2001 March (Box 17 (4.4.2-VHS), Folder 8)
      - Nightline, 1993 November (Box 17 (4.4.2-VHS), Folder 9)
      - Primetime Live Death Penalty Show (Box 17 (4.4.2-VHS), Folder 10)
      - Procedure 769, 1996 March (Box 17 (4.4.2-VHS), Folder 11)
      - "This Week with Sam Donaldson and Cokie Roberts" Televised Executions, 2001 April (Box 17 (4.4.2-VHS), Folder 12)
      - Why in the World -- Capital Punishment (Box 17 (4.4.2-VHS), Folder 13)
      - Witness to an Execution -- Aired on Hallmark Channel's "True North", 2001 August (Box 17 (4.4.2-VHS), Folder 14)